Bradan SchwankeMobile Engineer

Driven mobile engineer with professional experience in full-stack development for growing business. Highly knowledgeable in an array of languages, frameworks, and tools for web and mobile development to deliver helpful, effective, and visually pleasing applications.

Work Experience

Firmware Engineer at Control by Web

Developed embedded webpages for PLCs which implemented MQTT using Bootstrap and C. Wrote back-end software using the Laravel framework for communication between front-end interfaces and multiple cellular service APIs.

July 2023 - Current

Technical Support Agent at EFORCE Software

Addressed bugs presented by clients concerning the browser-based software. Used SQL to write queries to locate corrupt data in the client's database and perform commands to resolve the issue. Kept workload organized using Jira.

Feb 2022 - Sept 2022

Electrical Engineer Intern at iFIT Health & Fitness

Wrote embedded software and did testing for iFIT's fitness products. Main focus was using BLE and capacitive sensors to record and analyze data for runners.

May 2021 - Sept 2021

Education

Bachelor's of Science in Electrical Engineering Minor in Computer Science

Utah State University Logan, Utah 2017–2022

Contact

801-800-2444

bradanschwanke.work@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/bradanschwanke github.com/braysch Logan, Utah

Expertise

Mobile Development	(3y)
UI Design	(3y)
Back-end Development	(3y)
Programming	(7y)
Web Development	(3y)
API Integration	(1y)
Embedded Systems	(4y)
Database Management	(2y)

Skills

Android Studio	(3y)
Flutter	(2y)
Dart	(2y)
Java	(4y)
Kotlin	(3y)
Jetpack Compose	(3y)
JavaScript	(3y)
Bootstrap	(1y)
React	(1y)
Vue	(2y)
TypeScript	(1y)
HTML	(3y)

Passion

Time Management Attention to Detail Security Conscious Adaptability Problem Solving